We made it here in good time.
Master Catviper's a pretty
sharp navigator, isn't he?
Though I do suppose he sailed with
the King of the Pirates after all.
So, how long should we
wait at these ruins anyway?
I feel like it's been a while.
Until Master Catviper brings
Marco the Phoenix here, of course.
Yeah?
You think he'll do it?
I don't know.
I sure hope Marco comes
with us to the land.
of Wano the Phoenix would make
for a pretty powerful ally.
I mean this guy is the former first
edition commander of the infamous
Whitebeard Pirates so he's definitely
worth the effort of coming out here.
I was surprised to find out he's
one of Master Cat Vipers friends.
Good point.
If this Marco's such a celebrity then
I want to get a good look at him.
Whoa wait!
Let me remind you of something.
Master said to stay put because
of your intimidating looks.
Is Marco the kind of guy who
will get scared off by a face?
Listen here.
He was referring to that quaint little
village of peace-loving folks up there,
you Karoo fool.
Big, pearly warriors like
us will frighten the locals.
I see.
But Master Cadvipers' features are
scarier than mine, I would say.
Like when he's mad?
Yeah, but he does have a cute smile.
Too true.
There! Hey, wait!
Okay, he's all fixed up now.
You're good to go.
He said you're all better now.
Tama, feel good?
Don't push yourself too hard.
The flames of restoration only
have a slight effect on others.
Since I patched you up your natural
healing speed will be faster now.
You'll be bouncing around by tomorrow
It feels like you're back to normal.
Oh, boy!
Take it easy.
Set by tomorrow.
Thank you for the help, Marco!
We love you!
Marco? Excuse me.
I got a knot in my shoulder.
Marco, I saw a knot through the mouth.
Marco, the vest was an ideal.
Could you use some tears?
Marco, I slipped a disc in my back.
All right, all right.
I'll help you all, but
one at a time now, please
Pops built this village, you know.
So he took care of the people here?
Is that what you got, I mean?
Countries that are too poor to pay
heavenly tribute to the Celestial
Dragons are not allowed to join
the world government at all.
They tend to be lawless lands where
pirates and kidnappers run amok.
There's no one to stop them.
And when the country succumbs to collapse,
it turns out a fresh
generation of orphans.
Pops was one of those kids.
With nothing left to lose, he
went out to sea at an early age.
Even after becoming a pirate,
he cared about this island.
He'd funneled dirty money and
supplies here whenever he could,
but he never revealed who he was.
Did it till he died.
He never had a family, and his
friends were all long gone.
But this island was always home to him.
In a corrupt world, there's no
such thing as clean or dirty money.
It's just money.
Nice of you to say.
So after the war in Marineford,
at the very least we wanted to protect
this village that Pops loved so much.
That's why we started
a grudge war with Teach
when he tried to invade
our territory and claim it.
But we were no match for Teach,
especially after he stole Pops' power.
In the end, he took everything.
I wanted him to pay, and
I wanted to do it myself.
Poor Pops.
It's funny.
He was kind of a cheapskate.
He'd always mooch drinks off of others.
And the guy never once
offered to cover our tap.
And nobody said a thing
because we all knew
what he was doing with the money he saved.
He was sending it to the village.
Well, ain't that something?
So that makes this peaceful little spot
the last memento that he left behind,
doesn't it?
Yeah.
He must be grateful.
Red-haired Shanks made
sure to bury him here.
By the way, have you heard
of a warlord named Weevil?
He said he's Pops' biological son,
and now he's attacking people
connected to Whitebeard.
Wow, is her claim true?
I'm not sure, honestly.
Never knew his taste in women.
But if I had to guess,
they're after his fortune.
And I doubt they'd believe us
if we said there wasn't one.
And you know what?
It's a shame.
It's only a matter of time
before they come for this place.
I see that means you got our stuck here
Weevil's mother buckin was a
pirate back in her younger days
If I recall correctly, it must
have been about 30 or 40 years ago.
I even heard she used to be
on the very same ship as pops
And maybe you gotta have another
memento of his to protect
Not sure about that,
considering his behavior.
A fine pint!
If you're going to see Straw Hat Luffy
after this, can you pass on a message?
Nothing big.
Yeah, not a problem.
You said you're going to Wano? Yep.
Luffy, it says the referee kicked off.
Royalty from all over are attending.
They're at the conference
in Marie Joie right now.
All eyes are on a set
of guests who haven't
participated in two centuries
through a Yuku kingdom.
King Neptune will be in
attendance with all his children.
Ha!
Seems like Shirahoshi was
a big hit with everyone.
That means she went up
to the surface, huh?
She's getting tougher.
I'm proud of her.
It says here that your grandpa
was their personal escort.
Sounds like they're making arrangements
to relocate fishmen to the land.
Their dream's coming true.
Huh?
Vivi, my sweet!
You're even more
beautiful than I remember.
I just want to smooch ya.
What's that?
You want another?
Oh, do I get some change back?
Let me get in close.
Knock it off!
Vivi!
It's really her.
Wow, that's awesome.
It's been a while.
She looks so elegant and formal now.
Oh, I hope I get to meet her someday.
Do you think Vivi might be
interested in your mere panties?
I don't think so!
Oh, these are photos
of the Mingling Plaza.
Look at all the royal families.
Tons of bodyguards, too.
People from Dressrosa should
be there as well, right?
There she is, Viola!
Ugh! Waffle!
Hey, an acorn guy!
Huh? Waffle?
Why is he there?
That's Rebecca and Psy!
I know a lot of these guys!
No kidding.
Though I suppose any royalty we
know would be at the reverie.
That's kind of the point.
If that's the case,
then just maybe all the
princesses I've ever
met are in this same
place at the same time.
I bet they're all getting
excited talking about me.
You keep thinking that, buddy.
Chopper, look. Did you see?
Right there.
Chill, bro. What's going on?
It's Dr. Reed!
Ugh, the old bag's still alive.
Dr. Reed!
Hey, don't cut up the paper!
I wanted to save it, Chopper! Whoa!
Give me the section with the princesses.
What are you two doing?
You morons!
I wasn't finished reading it yet!
It's all full of holes now!
Oh, an article about Kaido?
And Big Mom 2?
Hang on.
Sanji, Chopper, give me
those pages back! Nuh-uh!
Glad to hear everyone's doing so good!
Once we're done sailing around
the world, let's go see them all.
Well, that sounds like a novel idea to me.
Anyway, back to getting things in order.
Have you tried to see if the
transponder snail can connect yet?
Ugh, I forgot.
Hey, this is Luffy.
Is anyone there?
No luck.
Nobody picked up.
Forget it. Let's go.
Hang on, Luffy.
What's wrong now?
Feel that wind?
This can't be a good sign.
I've never seen waves like those.
And the wind here is freezing cold.
But I think this is the sea around Wano.
Do you all feel how the wind keeps
getting stronger the closer we get?
And the waves only grow taller.
Take notice of how it's spinning.
That's not just from the wind currents.
That's a very unusual flow.
Look.
See how it's picking up over there?
I believe we should avoid the storm.
Maybe buy ourselves a little time?
What are you talking about, Brooke?
Don't worry about that junk.
Let's keep going.
But Luffy, why would you deliberately put
your crew in such a dangerous situation?
I don't know.
I think he's right.
When we left, Kin'emon did
give me a heads-up about this.
I'll explain it on the
auditory snail apparatus.
As you approach the land of Wano, you'll
find the entrance to be quite perilous.
The weather grueling, the
tides violently churning.
It's a difficult country to enter.
Huh?
The weather is always this awful?
I suppose we have no other
choice if that's the case.
And that's why we should just go!
There's Samurai warriors are mighty,
plus it's this hard to get into?
No wonder it's such an isolated country.
Hmm.
Let me think this over a little.
There has to be some way
to get us in there safely.
Yo!
What's that thing?
It's an octopus!
That guy's big!
Why is it on the ship?
Because we're at sea!
I realized that, Carrot!
Come on board!
Hey, while you're over there bickering,
those waters are pulling us in!
It doesn't matter!
Come on, Sunny!
Let's go to the Land of Water!
Hey, it looks like
something's coming towards us!
Uh-oh, what is it?
It kind of looks like a giant fish to me!
Is it a shark? Please, no!
It's Viggettus!
Koi fish?
Oh, wow, cool!
He's huge!
Yo!
A whole school of Goy.
What the hell are those
things doing in the sea?
They're freshwater fish.
How can they survive?
Who knows?
They're monsters anyway.
Hey, Saji, do these things fry up okay?
That stuff's not important right now.
I guess it's possible if you wash them
in hot water and then serve them chilled.
You can make our eye or I
can simmer them in some Miss.
I can batter them up and make tempura
or simmer them in sweet sauce.
Once we find the rest of the crew
let's celebrate with one of these.
Hey, don't struggle!
Of course it's gonna struggle!
You think it's gonna just let you eat it?
And Sanji,
you're the one who put this dumb idea
in his head, so you go bring him back!
It's not that big a deal.
We know he can manage on his own. Huh?
Let's just worry about
protecting the Sonny.
The wind is picking up!
Carrot, probe a tail! On it!
I need help!
Crazy look, how clean the water is?
It's crystal clear,
like a mountain stream.
I'd rather not see.
Thank you very much.
The giant fish are freaking me
out—is this a river? No way!
It looks like they're all
headed to the same place.
Hang on tight—we're just
along for the ride now!
ride now
There's movies on the road!
What the hell?
How's that possible?
The river's flowing into the waterfall,
not away from it, like usual.
I see.
There must be a massive freshwater
source at the top of the falls.
That's why it's not seawater.
I wonder, could that be 1-0 up there?
You think that's it?
None of this makes any sense!
I'm scared! It's terrifying!
Oh, cool!
The fish are climbing
the waterfall! They are!
Go Koi Fish!
I'm not sure how we can
get the Sunny up there.
We'll think if we take it head on.
Open to suggestions right now!
You're back!
Wow, you see that?
Those koi are tough!
You can admire the fish later!
Luffy, the ship's going to sink!
Right, I got this!
Huh?
You should probably hang on tight!
Leave the way, fish!
Are you kidding me?
Let's go!
Here we go!
We're doing it!
You know, I'm starting to think
Wano isn't going to be very nice.
I'm sick of this chaos.
Guys, that's the shore over there.
No, not awesome!
Loopy, let go of the fish! No, never!
They're my dinner!
I've had enough of you!
Ross, take the helm!
That's your wish, Nami!
No use!
The current's way too strong!
Damn it!
And we were almost there, too!
It was nice telling you!
Dr. Lean! I need it!
Where's my koi?
We're already floofy!
Oh no!
We're getting flushed!
Thank you.